[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "JJS", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNP", "WDT", "VBZ", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "Is it working or do enough people now know that it's kind of the horse has bolted?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "working", "or", "do", "enough", "people", "now", "know", "that", "it", "'s", "kind", "of", "the", "horse", "has", "bolted", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "CC", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "Well, it certainly look -- it makes it a lot more difficult to organize things if you can't use your cell phone, if you can't text people and obviously there's been no Internet for most people, no Facebook which is how these protests began seven days ago on the so-called day of rage.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "certainly", "look", "--", "it", "makes", "it", "a", "lot", "more", "difficult", "to", "organize", "things", "if", "you", "ca", "n't", "use", "your", "cell", "phone", ",", "if", "you", "ca", "n't", "text", "people", "and", "obviously", "there", "'s", "been", "no", "Internet", "for", "most", "people", ",", "no", "Facebook", "which", "is", "how", "these", "protests", "began", "seven", "days", "ago", "on", "the", "so-called", "day", "of", "rage", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "110131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "TO", "NN", "NNP", "VBZ", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "Your message to President Obama is what?", "question_tokens": ["Your", "message", "to", "President", "Obama", "is", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "My message to president Obama is -- and I have lots of respect for him.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "message", "to", "president", "Obama", "is", "--", "and", "I", "have", "lots", "of", "respect", "for", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1981"], "PERSON": ["Mubarak", "Anwar Sadat"], "LOCATION": ["U.S."]}, "docId": "110131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "CC", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "RB", ":", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "RB", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 69, "question": "So is it realty fair to criticize the administration now and President Obama now for not going against him or is it -- or do you understand their difficulties?", "question_tokens": ["So", "is", "it", "realty", "fair", "to", "criticize", "the", "administration", "now", "and", "President", "Obama", "now", "for", "not", "going", "against", "him", "or", "is", "it", "--", "or", "do", "you", "understand", "their", "difficulties", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", ":", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "Well, I don't -- you know when you hear protesters in the square, are they very concerned about whether or not it's fair from their vantage point the U.S. has been supporting a regime which has been corrupt, which has been arresting people, torturing people, and which has been not meeting their needs for some 30 years, certainly over the last 10 years or so -- remember, there's been a state of emergency in this country since Mubarak took office back in 1981 after the assassination of then President Anwar Sadat.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "--", "you", "know", "when", "you", "hear", "protesters", "in", "the", "square", ",", "are", "they", "very", "concerned", "about", "whether", "or", "not", "it", "'s", "fair", "from", "their", "vantage", "point", "the", "U.S.", "has", "been", "supporting", "a", "regime", "which", "has", "been", "corrupt", ",", "which", "has", "been", "arresting", "people", ",", "torturing", "people", ",", "and", "which", "has", "been", "not", "meeting", "their", "needs", "for", "some", "30", "years", ",", "certainly", "over", "the", "last", "10", "years", "or", "so", "--", "remember", ",", "there", "'s", "been", "a", "state", "of", "emergency", "in", "this", "country", "since", "Mubarak", "took", "office", "back", "in", "1981", "after", "the", "assassination", "of", "then", "President", "Anwar", "Sadat", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Tuesday"]}, "docId": "110131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "How do you feel the danger level has increased in the last 24 hours?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "the", "danger", "level", "has", "increased", "in", "the", "last", "24", "hours", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "Certainly it's been dangerous really since the first outbreak of massive protests on Tuesday.", "answer_tokens": ["Certainly", "it", "'s", "been", "dangerous", "really", "since", "the", "first", "outbreak", "of", "massive", "protests", "on", "Tuesday", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "I mean, Ben, are you able to get your family out even if you want to now or is it too late?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "Ben", ",", "are", "you", "able", "to", "get", "your", "family", "out", "even", "if", "you", "want", "to", "now", "or", "is", "it", "too", "late", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "Well, I don't want to get into the details, of the logistics of how to get them out.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "get", "into", "the", "details", ",", "of", "the", "logistics", "of", "how", "to", "get", "them", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "Ben, how many people do you think may actually turn out?", "question_tokens": ["Ben", ",", "how", "many", "people", "do", "you", "think", "may", "actually", "turn", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "It's difficult to say.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "difficult", "to", "say", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "POS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "Piers?", "question_tokens": ["Piers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "Ben, I completely agree that that's going to be an extraordinary day, I think.", "answer_tokens": ["Ben", ",", "I", "completely", "agree", "that", "that", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "an", "extraordinary", "day", ",", "I", "think", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Carter"], "LOCATION": ["United States", "Egypt"]}, "docId": "110131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "WDT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", ",", "RB", "VBN", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "Is that -- is that your reading of events over there?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "--", "is", "that", "your", "reading", "of", "events", "over", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", ":", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "Well, I'm not sure in what context President Carter said that, but I know for sure that many people are very, very worried, particularly in the United States and around the region that if instability comes to Egypt that will affect this region.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "sure", "in", "what", "context", "President", "Carter", "said", "that", ",", "but", "I", "know", "for", "sure", "that", "many", "people", "are", "very", ",", "very", "worried", ",", "particularly", "in", "the", "United", "States", "and", "around", "the", "region", "that", "if", "instability", "comes", "to", "Egypt", "that", "will", "affect", "this", "region", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Morgan"], "LOCATION": ["Egypt"]}, "docId": "110131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 185, "question": "What are your thoughts as you see the events unfurling in Egypt?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "your", "thoughts", "as", "you", "see", "the", "events", "unfurling", "in", "Egypt", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 186, "answer": "Before anything, Mr. Morgan, if you allow me to say that Egypt has a special place in my heart and my family's heart.", "answer_tokens": ["Before", "anything", ",", "Mr.", "Morgan", ",", "if", "you", "allow", "me", "to", "say", "that", "Egypt", "has", "a", "special", "place", "in", "my", "heart", "and", "my", "family", "'s", "heart", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Egypt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "DT", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "IN", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "And as such, I think it is time for the world to recognize that if we had had eras where leaders would make decisions or foreign (INAUDIBLE) would make decision, isn't it about time that we let the people make the decisions and have a choice?", "question_tokens": ["And", "as", "such", ",", "I", "think", "it", "is", "time", "for", "the", "world", "to", "recognize", "that", "if", "we", "had", "had", "eras", "where", "leaders", "would", "make", "decisions", "or", "foreign", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "would", "make", "decision", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "about", "time", "that", "we", "let", "the", "people", "make", "the", "decisions", "and", "have", "a", "choice", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NNS", "WRB", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "Isn't the problem with that is it's a great idea in theory, we all would agree with this, power to the people, give them what they want, as you know better than most.", "answer_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "the", "problem", "with", "that", "is", "it", "'s", "a", "great", "idea", "in", "theory", ",", "we", "all", "would", "agree", "with", "this", ",", "power", "to", "the", "people", ",", "give", "them", "what", "they", "want", ",", "as", "you", "know", "better", "than", "most", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "Have you or any of your family spoken to President Mubarak in the last week?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "or", "any", "of", "your", "family", "spoken", "to", "President", "Mubarak", "in", "the", "last", "week", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "AHLAVI: Not in recent weeks, of course.", "answer_tokens": ["AHLAVI", ":", "Not", "in", "recent", "weeks", ",", "of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mubarak"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "Do you think the people of Egypt now have the right to do what they are doing?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "the", "people", "of", "Egypt", "now", "have", "the", "right", "to", "do", "what", "they", "are", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "You know in my school of thought I have always been for people power and the right to self-determination.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "in", "my", "school", "of", "thought", "I", "have", "always", "been", "for", "people", "power", "and", "the", "right", "to", "self-determination", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Egypt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "I mean do you feel he's brought it on himself to a certain degree?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "do", "you", "feel", "he", "'s", "brought", "it", "on", "himself", "to", "a", "certain", "degree", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "Well, I think, you know, this is something for the Egyptian people to determine.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", ",", "you", "know", ",", "this", "is", "something", "for", "the", "Egyptian", "people", "to", "determine", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "How important has it been, do you think, social networking and Twitter in particular in getting the message out in Egypt?", "question_tokens": ["How", "important", "has", "it", "been", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "social", "networking", "and", "Twitter", "in", "particular", "in", "getting", "the", "message", "out", "in", "Egypt", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "AHLAVI: Well, I think since the electricity was invented it's the next best invention since then.", "answer_tokens": ["AHLAVI", ":", "Well", ",", "I", "think", "since", "the", "electricity", "was", "invented", "it", "'s", "the", "next", "best", "invention", "since", "then", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Egypt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "Do you find it easy to communicate via Twitter with people in Iran, for example?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "find", "it", "easy", "to", "communicate", "via", "Twitter", "with", "people", "in", "Iran", ",", "for", "example", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "You know, we have our ups and downs.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "we", "have", "our", "ups", "and", "downs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iran"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "You were there, weren't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "were", "there", ",", "were", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "I was.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "Do you fear that with the march tomorrow, that if these numbers are right, that millions turn out, that it would turn as nasty as it did then, with hundreds, maybe thousands of people getting killed?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "fear", "that", "with", "the", "march", "tomorrow", ",", "that", "if", "these", "numbers", "are", "right", ",", "that", "millions", "turn", "out", ",", "that", "it", "would", "turn", "as", "nasty", "as", "it", "did", "then", ",", "with", "hundreds", ",", "maybe", "thousands", "of", "people", "getting", "killed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "I don't think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "You met him three times?", "question_tokens": ["You", "met", "him", "three", "times", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "I think five or six times.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "five", "or", "six", "times", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", ",", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "What was he like when you first knew him?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "he", "like", "when", "you", "first", "knew", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "Very modest, almost to the point of being humble.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "modest", ",", "almost", "to", "the", "point", "of", "being", "humble", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "When Vice President Biden said he wasn't a dictator, did you agree with that?", "question_tokens": ["When", "Vice", "President", "Biden", "said", "he", "was", "n't", "a", "dictator", ",", "did", "you", "agree", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Biden"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "No one's quite sure what it is, yet, right?", "question_tokens": ["No", "one", "'s", "quite", "sure", "what", "it", "is", ",", "yet", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "I'm not quite sure myself.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "quite", "sure", "myself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "If you were President Obama right now, what would you now say?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "President", "Obama", "right", "now", ",", "what", "would", "you", "now", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "I'm glad I'm not because it's a real dilemma.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "glad", "I", "'m", "not", "because", "it", "'s", "a", "real", "dilemma", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Egypt"]}, "docId": "110131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "From your point of view as one of the senior business people in the world, what is doomsday and what is a good result from all that's happening?", "question_tokens": ["From", "your", "point", "of", "view", "as", "one", "of", "the", "senior", "business", "people", "in", "the", "world", ",", "what", "is", "doomsday", "and", "what", "is", "a", "good", "result", "from", "all", "that", "'s", "happening", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "NN", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "A really bad outcome is Egypt goes into chaos, that you get violence on the street.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "really", "bad", "outcome", "is", "Egypt", "goes", "into", "chaos", ",", "that", "you", "get", "violence", "on", "the", "street", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "How do you feel?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "Like everybody else, I have been taken by surprise.", "answer_tokens": ["Like", "everybody", "else", ",", "I", "have", "been", "taken", "by", "surprise", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]